♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Oh, my God, Brian, I went
to a baby rave last night.
Dropped a
Flintstones chewable.
It was a purple Betty.
I was flyin'!
I was up till
like... like...
I don't even
know how late.
Like, when I came home,
The Mentalist was still on.
Like, that's how late.
Morning, family.
Anyone needs me,
I'll be out in the yard
using my new riding mower.
A riding mower?
For God's sakes,
stop making all these
frivolous purchases.
You just blew
all that money
hiring that English-
to-raccoon translator.
(whispering
inaudibly)
(chittering)
(angry chittering)
Don't need a translator
for that one.
Tell him to come back when
he's ready to act like an adult.
Hey, what's up, Quagmire?
Oh, there's the
sound of the birds.
I thought they
all disappeared,
because all I could
hear was a lawnmower.
Oh, and what's that?
The wind in the trees!
Good-- that
still exists.
What are you doing there,
planting some flowers?
Hey, look, why don't you
go bother Joe, huh?
I can't. He's in Vegas
for the weekend,
seeing that handicapped
Cher impersonator.
♪ If I could turn back time ♪
♪ If I could find a way... ♪
Yeah! We all want
to turn back time!
This is the biggest
sitting ovation I've ever seen!
Damn it, where the hell
did I put that?
What are you
looking for, Brian?
That steak bone you
gave me last night.
I can't remember what
the hell I did with it.
Didn't you
bring it outside?
(clattering)
(screams)
Holy crap! Quagmire,
you all right?
No, I'm not all right!
My head's gushing
blood, you idiot!
Take your hand away.
Oh, boy! All right,
hold still, Quagmire.
(screams)
Oh, my God, a piece
of your brain came out!
Aah! Well, that
can't be good!
Well, maybe
it's not so bad.
I can feed it
to my pet zombie.
Here you go.
Yeah, you're hungry,
aren't ya?
He was a rescue.
When I found him,
he was just walking face-first
into a chain-link fence
downtown.
All right, almost
done here, Glenn.
There we are,
all finished.
Well, look at this.
Look what happened.
(chuckles)
Well, by the laws of
comedy, you and I have
to be roommates now.
That's hilarious, Doc.
All right, here we go.
Now, I'm going to prescribe
a course of antibiotics
and some painkillers and...
Hey, Elmer.
Hey.
She sucks.
Okay, Quagmire, before
we get your prescription,
let's grab some bandages.
God, this is such
an East Coast pharmacy.
How are we gonna find
gauze and bandages in the
middle of all this crap?
Uh, I think he keeps them
next to the thousand-piece
puzzle of a lobster trap.
I don't see it. You mean,
next to the Kadima paddles,
or next to the basic black
sweatshirt with no writing on it?
No, I think they're over
there between the rain
ponchos and the cap guns
and just below the
balsa wood gliders
and the net-bag of flip-flops
and a beach pail.
Above the set of jacks?
Yes, above the jacks and the
bicentennial playing cards
and across from the giant
cage with the beach balls,
next to the Wiffle ball bats
and the spark-spitting cars.
I don't... Oh, next to the
wax bottles of weird juice.
Yes, behind the plastic bag of
Mexican soldiers from the Alamo
and the Super Elastic
Bubble Plastic.
Oh, yeah, I got 'em.
Hey, Mort.
How's it going?
Oh, it's awful, Peter!
Why? What's the matter?
The pharmacy's going under.
I can barely pay my bills.
I can't even afford
the real pharmacy music.
That's just me up there. Listen.
MORT (a cappella):
♪ If this is it, ooh, wah,
please let me know ♪
♪ If this ain't love,
you better just say so ♪
♪ If this is it... ♪
They say I've got
Jewish honey in my voice.
Jewish honey is mucus.
But I thought you made
a lot of money here.
I used to,
but it's all gone downhill
since Muriel died.
She could get away
with overcharging people,
because they were always
mentally undressing her
and then re-dressing her
once they saw
the horrible mess underneath.
But in that interval,
she robbed them blind.
(sobbing)
Ooh.
Well, look, uh,
I don't know,
maybe there's
something we can do
to help you drum up
some business.
You know, get
the word out.
Like what?
Hey, you just
leave that to us.
(lively pop music playing)
(register ringing
in rhythm with music)
♪ ♪
(rhythmic ringing
and music crescendo)
(music stops)
(register ringing rhythmically)
Is opening and closing
the cash register
a bunch of times
helping business yet?
No.
Okay, then we'll do other stuff.
Okay, Mort, now, if you
want to get more customers
in your pharmacy, you're
gonna have to do a promotion,
like... like
"buy one, get one free."
What?
Buy one, get one free.
Huh?
Buy one...
Yeah, I get that.
Get one free.
Is that, like, a Spanish word?
No, it's English.
The whole thing's English.
Oh, 'cause it seems
like you're saying
the first part in English
and then some kind of made-up
pha-lumpf-phalumpf
or something in the second part.
I don't understand you.
All right, let me try
explaining it another way.
Let's say we're at
someone else's store,
and there's a sign, and it says:
"Buy one, get one free."
Get one free? Wow!
What store are
you talking about?
Excuse me, I have been
waiting for my prescription
for 25 minutes!
Oh, I'm really sorry,
Ms. Dumott.
We'll have that filled
for you right away.
Guys, what the hell's
going on back there?
Remember, each pill has
to go into the correct bottle.
(mechanical whirring)
Eh, this ain't so hard.
(whirring rises in pitch)
(whirring increases in pitch
as conveyor belt speeds up)
(whirring intensifying)
(vomits)
(woozily): I...
I got a wicked boner.
(thudding)
This was a great
idea, Peter.
We fly this thing
over Providence,
it's bound to get people
into the pharmacy.
That's right, bring
in the city folk
with their big money
and their long cigarettes
and their dogs with shoes.
Hey, check it out--
we got a giggity over
there on the 32nd floor.
I'm gonna go in
for a closer look.
QUAGMIRE:
Heh-heh, all right!
(gasps)
Quagmire, look out!
Oh, no!
Geez, that was a close one!
Yeah, but at least
nobody got hurt.
(tires squealing)
(clattering)
(burbling)
Goldman's Pharmacy!
Now, that could be a good place
to get new shoes for my dog.
Good evening, Quahog.
Grim details continue
to roll in at this hour
in the story of the detached
airplane advertising banner
which caused a school bus to
plummet into the Pawtuxet River.
That's right, Joyce.
Quahog's own Goldman's Pharmacy
made headlines
across the country
after a banner of theirs caused
the bus to drive off a bridge,
tragically killing
all the teenagers on board.
Many of the students
tweeted about the accident
as it was happening.
We have a few here.
From @Jenny94:
"Water seriously cold, yo."
Here's @TheTed69:
"I'm gonna survive this.
LOL jk."
"Jk," indeed.
Oh, God, I'm ruined!
Nobody's ever gonna shop
in my pharmacy again!
I'm gonna lose
everything!
Aw, gosh, Mort,
I feel terrible about this.
I wish there was
some way we could fix it.
You know, my cousin
had the same problem,
but he lucked out, 'cause his
business burned to the ground.
The insurance made him
a very rich man.
(chuckles) Too bad we can't
just torch the pharmacy.
Aw, come on, no,
we can't do that.
That'd be like stealing
from the insurance companies.
It wouldn't be right.
Aw, they're bastards.
Last year, after I lost
my beloved Muriel,
our life insurance company
refused to pay on her policy.
They took what should have been
a pleasant experience
and made it into an ordeal!
Well, that doesn't
totally surprise me.
A friend of mine
staying in my house
got, um, injured,
and my homeowner's insurance
wouldn't pay her doctor bills.
Said the policy didn't cover
an "act of rod."
Yeah, come to think of it,
they wouldn't even pay
for the fetus Lois lost
when we went to visit
the Museum of Staircases
and Spring-loaded Boxing Gloves.
Yeah, you know, they don't seem
to pay out on anything.
No, not at all, right?
Yeah, that's true, they don't pay.
Well, then I say,
screw the bastards!
Let's burn
the place down!
What?! Peter, we're talking
about a major crime here.
This is not smuggling Oriental
women into the country in steel cans.
This is a serious felony.
Quagmire, this whole
mess was our fault.
We got to make it right.
And, look, as long
as nobody sees us,
and we don't tell anybody,
then we're in the clear.
Well, I guess I did kind of
destroy your business, Mort.
All right, then let's do it--
tomorrow night!
Good. I'm just gonna
have to reschedule my
weekly re-circumcision.
So, what are we doing today,
a little off the top?
Yeah, but leave
a little up front
so I have something to play with.
Sounds good.
(unzips zipper) And take a look
at the back.
You see that there?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's trim that.
I don't know when
that started, but
let's get rid of that.
Okay, guys, listen up.
This is a very
flammable mixture
that's also
undetectable.
If we put it on the electric box
and two of the outlets,
then light them all at once,
it'll look like a short circuit.
Geez, Mort, how the hell do
you know how to do all this?
Oh, it's all covered in
the Torah.
Right after the chapter on
writing complaint letters
that will result in
compensatory merchandise.
Dear stuffed shirts
at Ritz Crackers.
A chain is only as strong
as its weakest link.
Just as a box of crackers
is only as appealing
as its least intact sleeve.
I am paying
for fully formed crackers,
not butter crumbles.
I don't buy your product
with broken quarters;
don't stick me
with broken pieces of cracker,
you miserable dicks!
Regards, Mort Goldman again.
All right, let's get to work.
♪ ♪
(explosion)
Oh, my God, we did it!
Hey, Peter, what
are you gonna tell Lois
when she asks
where you were tonight?
Don't worry, I got
it all covered.
(harsh braying)
(screeching bray)
Ha-ha!
This is awesome!
And Peter has no idea!
Well, Mr. Goldman,
we've ruled out foul play.
It looks like it was just
a case of faulty wiring.
Well, you're still gonna
have to buy something.
This is rubble,
not a library.
Okay, well...
I'm sorry for your loss,
but the good news is
your insurance
will be covering
all of your damages.
You hear what he said, fellas?
Looks like we pulled it off.
Yeah, for now.
I still got a
bad feeling.
He's gonna find something,
I just know it.
Will you relax?
We got an ironclad alibi.
We were all seeing The Beatles
live at The Ed Sullivan Show.
(song ends,
audience screaming)
(screams)
PETER:
Sorry. I rode a bike here.
All right, guys, all we got
to do now is keep a low profile
and not mention a word
of this to anybody.
Not even the police.
That's right,
not a word to anyone.
Nobody.
Lips are sealed.
I want to tell somebody.
Peter!
You shut your mouth!
Hey, Mort, I, uh,
was really sorry
to hear about
the pharmacy.
Oh, thank you, Joe.
I was very,
very sorry, too.
Yeah, he seemed pretty smart.
His shirt was tucked in,
so I bet he went to Harvard.
Well, you're my
friend, Mort.
I want you to know that
I'm going to personally
go over all
the evidence.
I'd hate to think
there's someone in town
who's out to get you.
Hey, Joe, they said
it was an accident.
Roll away.
No, I'm just saying,
as your friend, I
wouldn't feel right
unless I left no
stone unturned.
Geez, Joe, let it go.
Yeah, Joe, even Robocop
took a day off once in a while.
(phone ringing)
Nope.
(turns ringer off)
I don't like Joe sticking
his nose into this.
Maybe this was all
a big mistake.
You're damn right it was.
Why did I ever
agree to do this?
This isn't who I am.
I looked in the mirror
this morning, and it was like
I was looking at a man
I'd never seen before.
Hi.
Scott Bakula.
Just take it easy, Quagmire.
There's nothing to worry about.
(knocking)
JOE: Hey, it's Joe, open up.
(all gasp)
Uh, hey, Joe.
What's going on?
Oh, hey, I forgot,
I brought you guys
souvenirs from
my trip to Vegas.
They're T-shirts that say
"I lost my shirt in Lost Wages."
(laughing)
I think maybe
you should keep them.
All right,
I'll see you guys later.
I got to go see the forensics
team about the pharmacy.
Don't you worry, Mort.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
I don't like
this, you guys.
This is bad.
Joe's gonna find out,
I just know it.
Geez, Quagmire,
you need to relax.
And I know
how to help.
Calgon,
take him away.
(harp arpeggio)
QUAGMIRE: This is
worse, Peter!
Relax, this is supposed
to be your time.
This is the right way to
deal with your problems.
All right, guys,
if Joe really is nosing around,
I think I know how to get him
off the case once and for all.
(dialing)
JOE: Hello?
Officer Swanson,
this is the chief of police.
I'm afraid
you're fired.
I see. Well,
that's too bad.
I was looking forward
to giving you
your birthday present next week.
Oh.
Apparently,
there was a mistake.
Forget I called.
Guys, I got to become chief
of police by next week.
Chief, this just came in
for you from Officer Swanson.
A Starbucks gift card?!
This has been
an unproductive use of my time.
Okay, I got it.
Joe can't investigate
if he's distracted, right?
Well, what's more distracting
than texts about dinner plans?
Hmm. These burn ignition
patterns aren't consistent
with an electrical fire.
(phone chirps)
"Would... love to."
"Probably...
about 7:00... or 7:30."
(phone chirps, Joe sighs)
"Any... of...
those places would be... fine."
(phone chirps)
God! No way!
"I don't know
"Probably just
a collared shirt
"and jeans.
"Have you never been
to... a restaurant before?"
Oh, he's getting annoyed.
Look at that.
He sure is. Okay, now
tell him you want a vegan place.
(phone ringing)
Oh, my God,
he's so pissed, he's calling.
Well, answer it.
No, no, no.
I'm gonna send it to voicemail,
then call him back,
but pocket-dial him
while I walk a few blocks.
JOE (muffled,
from Peter's phone): Peter?
Peter? Hello?
I'm getting
very little work done!
You guys, I just can't
take this anymore.
I've been giving it
a lot of thought,
and I think
we all just need to confess.
What? Now just
hold on, Quagmire.
If you start yapping
to the cops,
we're gonna rot in prison
for the next 30 years.
JOE:
Evening, gentlemen.
(all gasp)
Joe!
Glad I found
you here.
I had a question
for you guys.
Did any of you happen
to be at Mort's pharmacy
on the night of the fire?
No.
None of us were.
I'm triplets. Could have
been one of my triplets.
I see. Well, then
it's kind of peculiar
that I would
find this.
A pocket-dial
voicemail from Peter
on the night
of the fire.
PETER: Oh, my God, look at that fire
we started, Quagmire and Mort.
You know
who I don't miss is Joe.
That's a piece of evidence
that hurts all of us.
You three are under arrest for
burning down Goldman's Pharmacy.
Well, the pocket-dial giveth,
and the pocket-dial taketh away.
You'll never take me alive!
Aren't you gonna run?
I would, but I don't want
my gym teacher to laugh at me.
He's been following me around
since junior high.
Watch this.
Watch this Jewish kid run.
First, I have to read you
the Miranda rights
for Jewish people.
You have the right to remain
silent, even though you won't.
You have the right to infer an
insult where none was intended.
What's that
supposed to mean?
You have the right to a lawyer,
who you are probably related to.
This interview
is over.
What were you dointhe night
of March 8th?
(Bleep) your mother.
Come on, man,
that's not cool.
Oh, yeah? Maybe this
is cool enough for you.
(farting)
(blows)
It's gonna take
a lot more
than a fart in my
face to make me...
Whoa! Whoa.
Yeah, and there's more
where that came from.
(straining)
(sighs)
No, there isn't.
Where were you
the night of the fire?
I was at the movies.
What did you see?
No Strings Attached.
How was it?
Sucked.
Okay, that checks out.
Boy, that Ashton Kutcher
sure was a cad
in that movie, wasn't he?
Yeah, totally.
Wrong! He had
a heart of gold.
You're going down.
Your husband's in here, ma'am.
Lois!
Peter, what's going on?
Is it true? Did you really
burn down Mort's pharmacy?
Hi, Lois. Hi.
Look, Lois, we were just trying
to help Mort.
Peter, how could you do this?
You have a family.
Did you ever stop
to think about us
before you did something that
could send you away to prison?
(sighs) For once, could you visit me
in jail and not criticize me?
Wait a minute.
This isn't Carvel,
you lying bitch.
All right,
that's enough.
Visiting time
is over.
You know you guys are
gonna do time for this.
Come on, Joe. You're really
gonna put us away?
You think I
want to do this?
You know how hard it's gonna be
for me to make new friends?
Hey, do you think Chris is
old enough to be my friend?
Old enough? Yes. But I wouldn't
bark down that alley.
You frighten him.
He thinks you're a Transformer
that broke halfway through.
I get that a lot.
I understand.
Look, Mort was
in trouble.
We-we were just trying
to help him out.
Well, insurance fraud is not
the way to help somebody out.
Listen, Joe, insurance agencies
are all scumbags.
They deserve to get hurt.
You don't decide that.
What you did is
against the law.
It's easy for you, Joe.
You don't know what it's like
to be screwed over
by an insurance company.
Oh, I don't, do I?
Well, let me tell you
a little story.
It was hours after my accident.
I was barely conscious
on the operating table,
but I'll never forget the phone
call that changed my life.
Hello, I'm calling on behalf of
your policyholder, Joe Swanson.
He's badly injured his spine.
Well, there's
a new procedure that,
if administered immediately,
should restore
his ability to walk.
$200,000.
We also have a wheelchair.
$60.
Okay.
They're going with "B."
Those sons of bitches
made it about money.
Yeah, Joe.
So, what do you say?
They didn't
care about you.
Why should you
care about them?
The thing is,
you guys committed a crime,
and I've still got the evidence
to prove it.
Too bad I lost it.
FEMALE AUTOMATED VOICE:
Message deleted.
Was that... was that supposed
to mean something?
Yeah, I'm letting
you guys go.
Oh. Oh, well,
that's great.
Yeah, I didn't
get that, either.
Yeah, why didn't you
just say that?
I'm starting to regret
erasing that message.
Too late, butt-face.
Have a great summer, Joe.
Peter, I don't
understand
how they just
let you out of jail.
Yeah, Joe had all kinds of
evidence against you guys.
Seems like a huge
miscarriage of justice.
I thought if you do
something wrong,
you're supposed
to get punished.
(laughing):
Oh, Chris, not if you're white.
Well, now that I've wrapped
things up with you guys,
I better wrap things up
with my basement family.
Well, did you guys
learn your lesson
about eating
uncooked antelope?
(hisses)
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru